i'm gonna teach you how to beatbox
so all you're gonna do is boots and cats
start with the word boots and focus on
making the bee as strong as possible
boots boots
boots boots boots boots and then all you
have to do is take out the vocalizations
next all you have to do is say any t
word like take time toaster and focus on
pronunciating the t as strong as you can
time time time time time time time and
like the b all you gotta do is drop the
vocalization time time time time
finally all you have to do is say cats
same as the two before you're gonna
focus on saying cats and pushing the sea
as strong as you can cats cats cats cats
cats cats cats
cats take out the vocalization cats cats
and with that you got the basics of
beatboxing the boots and cats
you